[
  { "id": 1, "front": "H", "back": "Hydrogen" },
  { "id": 2, "front": "He", "back": "Helium" },
  { "id": 3, "front": "Li", "back": "Lithium" },
  { "id": 4, "front": "Be", "back": "Beryllium" },
  { "id": 5, "front": "B", "back": "Boron" },
  { "id": 6, "front": "C", "back": "Carbon" },
  { "id": 7, "front": "N", "back": "Nitrogen" },
  { "id": 8, "front": "O", "back": "Oxygen" },
  { "id": 9, "front": "F", "back": "Fluorine" },
  { "id": 10, "front": "Ne", "back": "Neon" },
  { "id": 11, "front": "Na", "back": "Sodium" },
  { "id": 12, "front": "Mg", "back": "Magnesium" },
  { "id": 13, "front": "Al", "back": "Aluminum" },
  { "id": 14, "front": "Si", "back": "Silicon" },
  { "id": 15, "front": "P", "back": "Phosphorus" },
  { "id": 16, "front": "S", "back": "Sulfur" },
  { "id": 17, "front": "Cl", "back": "Chlorine" },
  { "id": 18, "front": "Ar", "back": "Argon" },
  { "id": 19, "front": "K", "back": "Potassium" },
  { "id": 20, "front": "Ca", "back": "Calcium" },
  { "id": 21, "front": "Sc", "back": "Scandium" },
  { "id": 22, "front": "Ti", "back": "Titanum" },
  { "id": 23, "front": "V", "back": "Vanadium" },
  { "id": 24, "front": "Cr", "back": "Chromium" },
  { "id": 25, "front": "Mn", "back": "Maganese" },
  { "id": 26, "front": "Fe", "back": "Iron" },
  { "id": 27, "front": "Co", "back": "Cobalt" },
  { "id": 28, "front": "Ni", "back": "Nickel" },
  { "id": 29, "front": "Cu", "back": "Copper" },
  { "id": 30, "front": "Zn", "back": "Zinc" }
]
